

ABOUT ME

A musician who codes!! Innovative, creative and a proven team player and a leader, seeking to secure position in software development and collaboratively share my skills, expertise and experience with team and valuable clients.

Started my career with front end development and went on to extend hands in backend along with database management, production servers maintenance/upgradations, team management.

7+ years experience in building platforms/products in data management/ingestion, data analytics & insights, marketing solutions business sector

SKILLS

Software System Knowledge

Engineering Principles

Agile Project Management

Team Building/ Management

Javascript / UI Frameworks

Java/.Net Core Programming

GCP

Docker/Kubernetes

UI/UX Designing

CONTACT

- +91-8281491678, +91-9140136803
- connect@ayushnair.in
- www.ayushnair.in
- Bengaluru

AYUSH NAIR

Engineering Manager
RESILIENT, COLLABORATOR, PATHFINDER

EDUCATION

College of Engineering, IHRD 2016

Bachelor's of technology in Computer Science

EXPERIENCE

TransUnion, Engineering Manager

2023 - Present

Leading & building the Analytics & insights team responsible for building platform for generating analytics and insights on Credit and non-credit data for credit marketing/risk use cases

Neustar Inc, Software Engineering Manager

2021 - 2023

Lead the Data Management team responsible for building capabilities for ingesting data from external locations and staging into enterprise data lake. Briefly also lead customer engineering for couple of quarters

Quero 3, Product lead/ Lead Eng/ Sr Eng

2018 - 2021

Built an ideal CDP platform for marketers, analysts and data scientists which helps to overcome the fragmentation of data, analytics and reporting systems

Dynactionize India, Software Engineer

2016 - 2018

Worked on four different projects developing UI screens using Angular which were focussed on showcasing the potential of Dynizer which was a database in its own.

ADDITIONAL ACTIVITIES

Ex-band member of Pank Rockers as a drummer.

Active band member of Ehsaass Music as an acoustic guitarist.